<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Menlo Lookaround</string>

    <string name="name_var">placeName</string>
    <string name="address_var">placeAddress</string>
    <string name="desc_var">placeDescription</string>
    <string name="img_var">placeImage</string>
    <string name="site_var">placeSite</string>
    <string name="loc_var">placeLocation</string>

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="more">For More Info</string>
    <string name="webpage">Website</string>

    <string name="map">Locate</string>
    <string name="sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee Shops</string>
    <string name="map_locations">Map Locations</string>

    <string name="menloPark">Menlo Park</string>
    <string name="homeOfFB">Home Of Facebook</string>


    <!-- Strings for all Restaurants -->

    <!-- Restaurant No. 1 -->
    <string name="R1_name_Evvia">Evvia</string>
    <string name="R1_address_Evvia">420 Emerson St, Palo Alto, CA 94301-1604</string>
    <string name="R1_desc_Evvia">Sister restaurant of Kokkari, Evvia has been serving beautiful and
        elegant Greek cuisine since 1995. Fabulous fish, savory roasted meats, and sun-soaked
        vegetables are jazzed up with a spritz of lemon, a little olive oil, and herbs.
        There is perfection in simplicity.</string>
    <string name="R1_site_Evvia">https://evvia.net/</string>
    <string name="R1_location_Evvia">37.4450585, -122.2338338</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 2 -->
    <string name="R2_name_Orens">Oren\'s Hummus Shop</string>
    <string name="R2_address_Orens">261 University Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94301-1714</string>
    <string name="R2_desc_Orens">Fresh and healthy is the name of the game here, where delicious
        bites are fired up with all natural ingredients and a lot of homemade love.</string>
    <string name="R2_site_Orens">http://www.orenshummus.com/</string>
    <string name="R2_location_Orens">37.445717, -122.1643617</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 3 -->
    <string name="R3_name_Refuge">The Refuge</string>
    <string name="R3_address_Refuge">Crane Street, Menlo Park, CA</string>
    <string name="R3_desc_Refuge">The REFUGE thrives in the quiet, unassuming towns of San Carlos,
        CA and Menlo Park, CA where the hand-carved, meltingly tender, boldly flavored navel
        pastrami is sending shockwaves through the gastronomic consciousness of patrons who call
        it “the greatest this planet will see in some time.</string>
    <string name="R3_site_Refuge">http://www.refugesc.com/</string>
    <string name="R3_location_Refuge">37.4515986, -122.1947601</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 4 -->
    <string name="R4_name_Tamarine">Tamarine Restaurant</string>
    <string name="R4_address_Tamarine">546 University Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94301-1901</string>
    <string name="R4_desc_Tamarine">Tamarine is a contemporary Vietnamese restaurant that features
        the light but flavor-intensive culinary delicacies of Vietnam. The restaurant offers a
        menu based on small plates, promoting the Vietnamese tradition of the \'shared\' meal in
        which food is shared and enjoyed with those close. Tamarine\'s small plate entrees are
        enjoyed with the pairing of a variety of aromatic, flavor infused rice, designed to be
        mixed and matched to create a truly unique flavor experience. Along with culinary delicacies
        of Vietnam, the restaurant showcases the works of emerging artists from Vietnam and other
        Southeast Asian countries.</string>
    <string name="R4_site_Tamarine">https://tamarinerestaurant.com/</string>
    <string name="R4_location_Tamarine">37.4488055, -122.2283774</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 5 -->
    <string name="R5_name_MenloGrill">Menlo Grill Bistro and Bar</string>
    <string name="R5_address_MenloGrill">100 El Camino Real, Menlo Park, CA 94025-5235</string>
    <string name="R5_desc_MenloGrill">A classic American grill with a warm and inviting neighborhood
        feel. The relaxed setting offers casual, yet sophisticated, dining with a menu that
        highlights regional and seasonal ingredients. An extensive wine-by-the-glass and craft brew
        selection is also featured.Open for breakfast, lunch, dinner and late night snacks.</string>
    <string name="R5_site_MenloGrill">http://www.menlogrill.com/</string>
    <string name="R5_location_MenloGrill">37.447625, -122.2417501</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 6 -->
    <string name="R6_name_Sundance">Sundance The Steakhouse</string>
    <string name="R6_address_Sundance">1921 El Camino Real, Palo Alto, CA 94306-1122</string>
    <string name="R6_desc_Sundance">Since its opening in 1974, prime steaks and martinis have never
        gone out of style at this Palo Alto institution. The atmosphere is very clubby with
        fireplaces, dark wood, sports memorabilia and plush leather booths tucked into the many
        nooks throughout the dining room. Famous for their slow-roasted prime rib &amp; hand-cut
        U.S.D.A Prime Steaks, they also offer fresh seafood, cold water lobster tail &amp; succulent
        shellfish. The 23 oz. Bone-In Rib eye Steak is the \"Boss\' Favorite\" while the Double Cut
        Filet Mignon runs a close second. Sundance is respected for serving the best food money can
        buy coupled with value &amp; simplicity – a welcome relief for serious food &amp; steak
        aficionados. The menu is supported by an award-winning wine list that features over 400
        selections focusing on highly allocated Napa Valley Cabernets &amp; Sonoma Pinot Noirs.
        Exceptional ratings &amp; numerous restaurant awards rank Sundance the Steakhouse as a true
        dining destination.</string>
    <string name="R6_site_Sundance">http://www.menlogrill.com/</string>
    <string name="R6_location_Sundance">37.4285178, -122.2196353</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 7 -->
    <string name="R7_name_Madera">Madera</string>
    <string name="R7_address_Madera">2825 Sand Hill Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025</string>
    <string name="R7_desc_Madera">Madera Restaurant Honored with One Star by Michelin and Wine
        Spectator\'s Best of Award of Excellence 2012. A comfortably elegant ambiance, picturesque
        views and outdoor terraces welcome guests and Silicon Valley locals to Madera. Featuring an
        open artisan wood-burning kitchen and extensive wine list, Madera serves rustic American
        cuisine that celebrates the culinary traditions of the Bay Area In addition to indoor and
        outdoor dining, Madera offers two private dining rooms with private terraces and cozy
        fireplaces. The Lemon Room seats up to 10 guests, and the Orange Room up to 14 guests. This
        Menlo Park restaurant is open daily for breakfast, lunch and dinner and for Sunday brunch as
        well.</string>
    <string name="R7_site_Madera">http://www.maderasandhill.com/</string>
    <string name="R7_location_Madera">37.4197281, -122.2150898</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 8 -->
    <string name="R8_name_Flea">Flea Street Cafe</string>
    <string name="R8_address_Flea">3607 Alameda de las Pulgas, West Menlo Park, CA 94025</string>
    <string name="R8_desc_Flea">A restaurant which makes a difference by using food and wine raised,
        harvested, and produced sustainably and regionally. Buying locally provides great quality,
        boosts our economy, protects our farmland, enhances our local food systems, and keeps us
        and our environment healthy. We support and use as many organic ingredients as possible-those
        produced without petrochemicals, artificial coloring, growth stimulants, antibiotics or
        pesticides.</string>
    <string name="R8_site_Flea">https://www.cooleatz.com/flea-st-cafe</string>
    <string name="R8_location_Flea">37.4318449, -122.203307</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 9 -->
    <string name="R9_name_Stacks">Stacks</string>
    <string name="R9_address_Stacks">600 Santa Cruz Ave, Menlo Park, CA 94025-4503</string>
    <string name="R9_desc_Stacks">A restaurant whose menu items, the simple American classics, are
        homemade with farm fresh eggs, real butter, and heavy cream. Our fruits and vegetables are
        market fresh. We use only the highest quality of Midwest Hormel meat products, such as our
        apple-wood smoked bacon and our honey hams. We use the famous Aidells\' chicken apple sausage,
        and our burgers are #1 USDA Choice Angus, fresh, never frozen.</string>
    <string name="R9_site_Stacks">http://www.stacksrestaurant.com/HP_static.html</string>
    <string name="R9_location_Stacks">37.4534159, -122.1855036</string>

    <!-- Restaurant No. 10 -->
    <string name="R10_name_SqueezeIn">Squeeze In</string>
    <string name="R10_address_SqueezeIn">3710 Florence St, Redwood City, CA 94063–4418</string>
    <string name="R10_desc_SqueezeIn">At just 10 feet, 3 inches wide, and with only 39 seats, guests
        would literally have to \'squeeze in\' to enjoy their breakfast at the little restaurant. As
        the list of omelette options grew, so did the popularity of the restaurant, and by the mid
        80\'s it was considered a true Truckee institution. Not some business, not a restaurant,
        THIS restaurant: the Squeeze In. Between the scrumptious food, the signatures on the wall,
        and the undeniable hippie vibe, they knew that it was one day their destiny.</string>
    <string name="R10_site_SqueezeIn">https://www.squeezein.com/</string>
    <string name="R10_location_SqueezeIn">37.4787187, -122.1891855</string>


    <!-- Strings for all Sights -->

    <!-- Sight No. 1 -->
    <string name="S1_name_Facebook">Facebook Headquarters</string>
    <string name="S1_address_Facebook">Facebook Headquarters, 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S1_desc_Facebook">Whether you \'like\' it or not, Facebook has pretty much taken
        over the world and all of our social lives just within the past few years, and it all
        started in the small city of Menlo Park. An iconic Silicon Valley site and hometown success,
        the original Facebook Headquarters is a must-see if you\'re visiting the Peninsula. Snap a
        pic next to the big thumbs-up and be THAT person on your high school friends\' news feeds.</string>
    <string name="S1_site_Facebook">https://www.facebook.com/</string>
    <string name="S1_location_Facebook">37.4847086, -122.1499346</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 2 -->
    <string name="S2_name_Keplers">Kepler\'s Books</string>
    <string name="S2_address_Keplers">Kepler\'s Books, 1010 El Camino Real, Menlo Park, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S2_desc_Keplers">Dating back to 1955, this independent bookstore is a local
        landmark. Due to the decline of sales at bookstores in general, Kepler\'s found itself in the
        same situation as many bookstores and had been forced to close in 2005. Thousands of loyal
        customers and local community members responded with demonstrations on the plaza and, within
        weeks, Kepler\'s was back! With several events happening all the time, it isn\'t uncommon to
        see well-known authors at a signing. Local celebs like Betsy Franco [James Franco\'s mom] and
        even James himself have also been known to stop at Kepler\’s.</string>
    <string name="S2_site_Keplers">http://www.keplers.com/</string>
    <string name="S2_location_Keplers">37.453569, -122.1843557</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 3 -->
    <string name="S3_name_CheekyMToys">Cheeky Monkey Toys</string>
    <string name="S3_address_CheekyMToys">Cheeky Monkey Toys, 640 Santa Cruz Ave, Menlo Park, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S3_desc_CheekyMToys">Locally owned by Anna and Dexter Chow, Cheeky Monkey Toys is
        a paradise for kids of all ages. Lining the front counters, it\'s like a real life Zonko\'s
        Joke Shop with fun little gag gifts like fake vomit and whoopee cushions for the immature
        inner child in all of us. From Legos and Hot Wheels to all the latest in Princess dress-up
        chic, this mom-and-pop store has got it all and more.</string>
    <string name="S3_site_CheekyMToys">https://www.cheekymonkeytoys.com/</string>
    <string name="S3_location_CheekyMToys">37.4528571, -122.1839578</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 4 -->
    <string name="S4_name_SharonPark">Sharon Park</string>
    <string name="S4_address_SharonPark">Sharon Park, 1100 Monte Rosa Drive, Menlo Park, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S4_desc_SharonPark">With such amazing weather in the Bay Area, sometimes you just
        want to be outside to soak in all in. Just before the Stanford Hills, Sharon Park is a
        hidden oasis and a well-kept local secret. Just off of Sand Hill Road and tucked behind some
        trees, the park is centered around a gorgeous peaceful lake with grassy areas ideal for an
        afternoon picnic. A popular spot among folks with kids, the park has a small playground for
        the youngsters and a quiet gazebo on the lake for Mom and Dad.</string>
    <string name="S4_site_SharonPark">null</string>
    <string name="S4_location_SharonPark">37.4238917, -122.2114051</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 5 -->
    <string name="S5_name_Guild">The Guild</string>
    <string name="S5_address_Guild">The Guild Theatre, 949 El Camino Real, Menlo Park, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S5_desc_Guild">Dating back to 1926, The Guild is a historic local theater that
        will transport you back in time. Popular mostly with an older crowd, this movie theater has
        been getting a lot of buzz recently among twenty-somethings. The retro little theater is
        also a really fun place to meet new people with similar interests at different shows. There
        are a lot of screenings of cult favorites like Rocky Horror Picture Show as well as indie
        and foreign films which make for fun date nights and a great place to hang out with old friends.</string>
    <string name="S5_site_Guild">www.guildtheatre.co.za/</string>
    <string name="S5_location_Guild">37.4524412, -122.1834688 </string>

    <!-- Sight No. 6 -->
    <string name="S6_name_DutchGoose">The Dutch Goose</string>
    <string name="S6_address_DutchGoose">The Dutch Goose, 3567 Alameda De Las Pulgas, Menlo Park, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S6_desc_DutchGoose">If you\'re new in town or want to grab a drink with co-workers,
        the Dutch Goose is your premier destination. Inside, you\'ll find a classic bar scene with
        your basic burgers-and-fries kind of menu to go with the ice cold beers on tap. It isn\'t the
        menu people come for, though. Besides the usual TV\'s, there are some cool old-school arcade
        games that remind you that this hangout has been around since the 1960\'s. Behind the building,
        there is a heated patio area where everyone hangs out and mingles. It\'s like a backyard BBQ
        with a hundred new friends.</string>
    <string name="S6_site_DutchGoose">http://www.dutchgoose.net/</string>
    <string name="S6_location_DutchGoose">37.4320507, -122.2037716</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 7 -->
    <string name="S7_name_DrivingThrAtherton">Driving Through Atherton</string>
    <string name="S7_address_DrivingThrAtherton">Atherton, CA, USA</string>
    <string name="S7_desc_DrivingThrAtherton">Just past the city limits of Menlo Park, there is a
        little town called Atherton. If it sounds familiar, it might be because it was named the
        richest zip code in the entire country in the year 2015. Gorgeous mansions and beautiful
        estates line the streets of this posh little suburban town. Driving through Atherton,
        you\'ll see the reality that is the thriving tech movement when you pass the homes of several
        noted Silicon Valley entrepreneurs and moguls.</string>
    <string name="S7_site_DrivingThrAtherton">null</string>
    <string name="S7_location_DrivingThrAtherton">37.4497917,-122.2353955</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 8 -->
    <string name="S8_name_PaceAnT">Pace Art and Technology</string>
    <string name="S8_address_PaceAnT">300 El Camino Real, Menlo Park, CA 94025-5239</string>
    <string name="S8_desc_PaceAnT">Pace Art &amp; Technology, founded by Pace President Marc Glimcher,
        is the gallery\'s new program dedicated to collaboration with interdisciplinary art groups,
        collectives and studios whose works explore the confluence of art and technology. The program
        is an expansion of Pace\'s longstanding commitment to artistic approaches that emphasize
        digital and technological methods.</string>
    <string name="S8_site_PaceAnT">http://www.pacegallery.com/</string>
    <string name="S8_location_PaceAnT">37.4492117, -122.2446009</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 9 -->
    <string name="S9_name_AutoVino">AutoVino</string>
    <string name="S9_address_AutoVino">205 Constitution Dr, Menlo Park, CA 94025-1108</string>
    <string name="S9_desc_AutoVino">AutoVino is a state-of-the-art luxury car and fine wine storage
        facility. Mr. Giurlani, part of a family olive oil import business in San Francisco has a
        penchant for classic, and luxury cars. Trouble is he soon needed a place to store them.
        Not finding anything satisfactory, he built one. Climate controlled, dust free and offering
        services tailored to fine car owners (hand washing after a Sunday drive), he now has rare
        museum quality cars, exotics and \"cherry\" muscle cars parked in his showroom. This concept
        is so popular he offers club memberships. His Woodside Vineyards winery and winemaker is
        here too and he stores wine collections for oneophiles.</string>
    <string name="S9_site_AutoVino">http://auto-vino.com/</string>
    <string name="S9_location_AutoVino">37.4833064, -122.2401453</string>

    <!-- Sight No. 10 -->
    <string name="S10_name_MilitaryVT">Military Vehicle Tech. Foundation</string>
    <string name="S10_address_MilitaryVT">419 Old Spanish Trl, Menlo Park, CA 94028-8133</string>
    <string name="S10_desc_MilitaryVT">The Military Vehicle Technology Foundation oversees one of
        the largest and most significant collections of historical military vehicles in the world.
        Our goal is to acquire, restore, and interpret the historical significance of 20th and 21st
        century military vehicles. Domestic and foreign combat vehicles such as tanks, armored cars,
        self-propelled artillery, and other technically interesting mobile platforms are the focus
        of the collection. We maintain an extensive technical library that describes many vehicles
        down to the part level. Aside from the vehicles, there are towed artillery, antitank, and
        antiaircraft guns.</string>
    <string name="S10_site_MilitaryVT">http://www.mvtf.org/</string>
    <string name="S10_location_MilitaryVT">37.335549, -122.1926127</string>


    <!-- Strings for all Landmarks -->

    <!-- Landmark No. 1 -->
    <string name="L1_name_Fremont">Fremont Park</string>
    <string name="L1_address_Fremont">Santa Cruz Avenue &amp; University Dr, Menlo Park, CA 94025</string>
    <string name="L1_desc_Fremont">Located in the heart of Fremont, Central Park — Lake Elizabeth
        offers a variety of activities with a gorgeous view of the Mission Peak Hills and Lake
        Elizabeth. Central Park is set on 450+ acres with an 80+ acre lake and 2 mile pedway around
        the lake. The park has much to offer including reserved picnic sites, drop-in picnic sites,
        children\'s play areas, basketball, tennis, fishing, skate park, and seasonal waterpark
        (Aqua Adventure Waterpark), boat rentals, launches, and storage. Our facilities and picnic
        areas create a perfect atmosphere for any occasion — from Birthday Parties, Family /
        Corporate Picnics or BBQ, Baby Showers, Anniversaries, Family Reunions, and more!</string>
    <string name="L1_site_Fremont">https://www.fremont.gov/317/Central-Park</string>
    <string name="L1_location_Fremont">39.1972692, -124.010499</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 2 -->
    <string name="L2_name_PaloAltoTW">The Palo Alto Tower Well</string>
    <string name="L2_address_PaloAltoTW">201 Alma St, Palo Alto, CA 94301</string>
    <string name="L2_desc_PaloAltoTW">At one point, it was close to becoming a tall, cylindrical
        single-family home, a museum or a day care center. In the end, the historic Tower Well,
        Palo Alto\'s first water tower, is going to keep its original identity. The tower, built in
        1911 to hold the city\'s water supply, will now be surrounded by a park and plaza. The tower
        has 7-foot to 10-foot thick walls with steel reinforcements. The upper 25 percent of the
        tower was used to store 155,000 gallons of water supplied by the now abandoned well on the
        corner of the site.</string>
    <string name="L2_site_PaloAltoTW">https://www.paloaltoonline.com/weekly/morgue/news/2000_Apr_5.TOWER.html</string>
    <string name="L2_location_PaloAltoTW">37.4256293, -122.2053904</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 3 -->
    <string name="L3_name_Hanna">Hanna House</string>
    <string name="L3_address_Hanna">737 Frenchmans Rd, Stanford, CA 94305</string>
    <string name="L3_desc_Hanna">Hanna House was designed by Frank Lloyd Wright in 1936 for Stanford
        Professor Paul Hanna and his wife, Jean, specialists in childhood education. Wright had
        become interested in designing elegant and affordable homes for the American middle class to
        create a more harmonious, enlightened society. The long-term collaboration between the Hannas
        and Wright resulted in an unprecedented design: a house based on hexagonal geometry, with no
        right angles in the floor plan. This radical experimentation allowed Wright to explore open
        spatial planning. Hanna House was a turning point in his career, leading to ideas later
        evidenced in the Guggenheim Museum in New York. The Hannas lived in the house until giving
        it to Stanford in 1975. It housed four university provosts until suffering severe damage in
        the 1989 Loma Prieta earthquake. It underwent complex restoration, made complicated by its
        unique design, and reopened to the public in 1999.</string>
    <string name="L3_site_Hanna">https://hannahousetours.stanford.edu/</string>
    <string name="L3_location_Hanna">38.377139, -122.7486817</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 4 -->
    <string name="L4_name_AngelOG">Angel of Grief</string>
    <string name="L4_address_AngelOG">Near Intersection of Palm Dr &amp; Arboretum Rd, Stanford University,
        Stanford, CA 94305</string>
    <string name="L4_desc_AngelOG">Not long ago, the mourning \"Angel of Grief\" statue that marks the
        Arboretum grave of Jane Stanford\'s brother Henry Clay Lathrop was truly a sorrowful sight.
        An act of vandalism had stolen the angel\'s left arm and left a rusting piece of iron sticking
        out of the marble. The wingtips and some of the fingers on the lichen-stained angel\'s
        remaining arm were missing, and the black-and-white terrazzo tile around the base was crumbling.
        In fact, the whole area - a quiet section of the Arboretum once planned as the site of the
        Stanfords\' country mansion — was in sad shape six years ago when Chris Christofferson,
        now director of Facilities Operations, came to campus for a job interview.</string>
    <string name="L4_site_AngelOG">http://news.stanford.edu/news/2001/april18/mausoleum-418.html</string>
    <string name="L4_location_AngelOG">37.4324212, -122.1736371</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 5 -->
    <string name="L5_name_StoneRiverAG">Stone River - Andy Goldsworthy</string>
    <string name="L5_address_StoneRiverAG">Stanford University, Palm Dr &amp; Museum Way, Stanford, CA 94035</string>
    <string name="L5_desc_StoneRiverAG">Stone River is a wall-like serpentine sculpture set in about
        three acres of land to the northeast of the Iris &amp; B. Gerald Cantor Center for Visual Arts.
        It is about 3 1/2 feet high and about 4 feet wide at its base. It is made of more than 6,500
        stones, including about 700 triangular coping stones weighing between 20 and 50 pounds each
        that top the sculpture. Each coping stone was individually shaped at a different angle to
        fit the wall precisely. The total weight of the piece is about 128 tons. Goldsworthy first
        visited Stanford over a year ago to choose the site and consider the project. It was his
        vision to employ stone that had a relationship to the university.</string>
    <string name="L5_site_StoneRiverAG">https://museum.stanford.edu/news_room/archived_acquisitions_goldsworthy.html</string>
    <string name="L5_location_StoneRiverAG">37.4332523, -122.1715022</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 6 -->
    <string name="L6_name_Rengstorff">Rengstorff House</string>
    <string name="L6_address_Rengstorff">3070 N Shoreline Blvd, Mountain View, CA 94043</string>
    <string name="L6_desc_Rengstorff">The Rengstorff House is Mountain View\'s oldest historic house
        and is one of the finest examples of Victorian Italianate architecture on the West Coast.
        While the Rengstorff House is a wonderful example of architecture in its own right, it is
        also a prime model of adaptive reuse. Today this beautifully restored historic house museum
        provides the perfect setting for visitors to acquaint themselves with the attributes of the
        19th century. The Friends of \"R\" House invite you come to the Rengstorff House and experience
        one of a kind exhibits, living history programs, memorable holiday events, and much more.</string>
    <string name="L6_site_Rengstorff">http://r-house.org/</string>
    <string name="L6_location_Rengstorff">37.4314795, -122.089319</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 7 -->
    <string name="L7_name_HP">HP Garage</string>
    <string name="L7_address_HP">367 Addison Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94309</string>
    <string name="L7_desc_HP">In 1938 David and Lucile Packard got married and rented the first floor
        of the house at 367 Addison Avenue in Palo Alto. The simple one car garage became the HP
        workshop and the little shack out back became Bill Hewlett\'s home. In 1989 California named
        the garage \"the birthplace of Silicon Valley\" and made it a California Historical Landmark.
        This home was built in 1905 and remained a rental property throughout most of its existence.
        In 2000, HP decided that they needed to acquire the house so they could properly preserve
        its history. What was a modest middle class home in the 1930s was bought for 1.7 million
        dollars in 2000. Over the next 5 years, the house was restored back to what it was like in
        1939 (except where compliance with modern code didn\'t allow.) In 2007, the property was
        added to the National Register of Historic Places.</string>
    <string name="L7_site_HP">http://www.hpmuseum.org/garage/garage.htm</string>
    <string name="L7_location_HP">37.4430328, -122.156808</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 8 -->
    <string name="L8_name_HooverT">Hoover Tower</string>
    <string name="L8_address_HooverT">550 Serra Mall, Stanford, CA 94305</string>
    <string name="L8_desc_HooverT">At the top of the tower, visitors can see a carillon of 48 bells.
        The original 35 bells were cast of bronze in Tournai, Belgium, and were a gift of the
        Belgian-American Education Foundation. The largest bell of the original 35 is inscribed,
        \"UNO PRO PACE SONO\" which means \"for peace alone do I ring\". Following a two-year refurbishment
        at the Royal Eijsbouts foundry in the Netherlands, the carillon returned to the tower in 2002.
        The restoration replaced eleven bells with newly cast ones and the addition of thirteen bells
        increased the instrument\'s range to four octaves. With a new keyboard and 48 bells tuned to
        concert pitch, the carillon makes beautiful music for special university events.</string>
    <string name="L8_site_HooverT">http://visit.stanford.edu/plan/guides/hoover.html</string>
    <string name="L8_location_HooverT">37.4276114, -122.1691601</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 9 -->
    <string name="L9_name_CourthouseSq">Courthouse Square</string>
    <string name="L9_address_CourthouseSq">2200 Broadway, Redwood City, CA 94063</string>
    <string name="L9_desc_CourthouseSq">Courthouse Square is a backlot located at Universal Studios.
        The set is composed of several facades that form an archetypal American town square with a
        courthouse as its centerpiece. The set is most famous for being featured as downtown Hill
        Valley in the Back to the Future trilogy, and as Kingston Falls in the Gremlins series.
        Prior to the Back to the Future series, the area was known as Mockingbird Square due to its
        role in the film To Kill a Mockingbird. It has been severely damaged by fire several times,
        including in 1957, 1990 and 2008. It was reconstructed after each incident.</string>
    <string name="L9_site_CourthouseSq">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Courthouse_Square</string>
    <string name="L9_location_CourthouseSq">39.396581, -76.5887717</string>

    <!-- Landmark No. 10 -->
    <string name="L10_name_Lathrop">Lathrop House</string>
    <string name="L10_address_Lathrop">627 Hamilton St, Redwood City, CA 94063</string>
    <string name="L10_desc_Lathrop">Lathrop House is located in the center of Redwood City\'s
        downtown area at 627 Hamilton Avenue, behind the old Domed Courthouse and opposite the Hall
        of Justice which is built on the site of \"California Square\" – a Spanish plaza style park –
        deeded to the citizens of Redwood City in perpetuity by the original landholders; the Arguello
        family and Mezes family. One of the Peninsula\'s oldest mansions, Lathrop House is an
        architectural treasure built in 1863 by San Mateo County\'s first assessor-clerk-recorder and
        chairman of the Board of Supervisors, a man who later helped found the Southern Pacific
        Railroad and owner of a large tract of land in the Menlo Park area</string>
    <string name="L10_site_Lathrop">http://www.lathrophouse.org/</string>
    <string name="L10_location_Lathrop">37.487956, -122.232132</string>


    <!-- Strings for all Coffee Shops -->

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 1 -->
    <string name="C1_name_CBorrone">Cafe Borrone</string>
    <string name="C1_address_CBorrone">1010 El Camino Real #110, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA</string>
    <string name="C1_desc_CBorrone">Great food in downtown Menlo Park. Nice patio for
        enjoying the great weather.  Good sandwiches and salads. Ingredients are fresh. Great place
        to have a morning coffee or sit in the sun with afternoon tea or beer!</string>
    <string name="C1_site_CBorrone">http://www.cafeborrone.com/</string>
    <string name="C1_location_CBorrone">37.4536631, -122.2519892</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 2 -->
    <string name="C2_name_Jasons">Jason\'s Cafe</string>
    <string name="C2_address_Jasons">1246 El Camino Real, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA</string>
    <string name="C2_desc_Jasons">A classic American grill with a warm and inviting neighborhood
        feel. The relaxed setting offers casual, yet sophisticated, dining with a menu that
        highlights regional and seasonal ingredients. An extensive wine-by-the-glass and craft brew
        selection is also featured.Open for breakfast, lunch, dinner and late night snacks.</string>
    <string name="C2_site_Jasons">null</string>
    <string name="C2_location_Jasons">37.454862, -122.1871856</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 3 -->
    <string name="C3_name_Coupa">Coupa Cafe</string>
    <string name="C3_address_Coupa">538 Ramona St, Palo Alto, CA 94301-1709</string>
    <string name="C3_desc_Coupa">Coupa café on Ramona avenue has a charm of its own. The place itself
        has a historic feel and the venezuelian specialties are very tasty. The salads and pastas are
        also very good. My favorite salads are the Beverly and the Cobb and among the pastas I
        recommend the chicken alfredo. Very nice place also to enjoy a glass of wine and a light
        dinner in the evening.
</string>
    <string name="C3_site_Coupa">http://www.coupacafe.com/</string>
    <string name="C3_location_Coupa">37.4446074, -122.2315842</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 4 -->
    <string name="C4_name_MColette">Mademoiselle Colette</string>
    <string name="C4_address_MColette">816 Santa Cruz Ave, Menlo Park, CA 94025-4610</string>
    <string name="C4_desc_MColette"> Debora Ferrand is the owner/founder of Mademoiselle Colette.
        She has graduated from the « Cordon Bleu »,and has further developed an innate inspiration
        for delicate pastries by attending the national school of Pastry in France (School of Alain Ducasse)
        where she rubbed shoulders with chef Jean-Marie Hiblot, of the well known Plaza Athene in Paris.
        Well World Traveled, Debora has continued to innovate and come up with new creations, inspired
        by her many different cultural experiences while constantly remaining dedicated to her
        ultimate French flair. </string>
    <string name="C4_site_MColette">http://www.mademoisellecolette.com/</string>
    <string name="C4_location_MColette">37.4508996, -122.1876101</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 5 -->
    <string name="C5_name_AnnsCoffee">Ann\'s Coffee Shop</string>
    <string name="C5_address_AnnsCoffee">772 Santa Cruz Ave, Menlo Park, CA 94025–4514</string>
    <string name="C5_desc_AnnsCoffee">This place has been around for a long time and the food is great.
        Ann\'s changed hands years ago but never missed a step of quality.
        The eggs seem to be single cracked and the pancakes are memorable. The staff are pleasant
        and always willing to just do the extra.</string>
    <string name="C5_site_AnnsCoffee">null</string>
    <string name="C5_location_AnnsCoffee">37.4513549, -122.1873555</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 6 -->
    <string name="C6_name_PBaguette">Paris Baguette</string>
    <string name="C6_address_PBaguette">383 University Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94301–1717</string>
    <string name="C6_desc_PBaguette">We provide great coffee and pastries, atmosphere resembling a
        French bar. Most people like to spend their breakfast time here, working on their laptops or
        reading a newspaper - free internet wifi connection available. We are always open,
        including on Sundays and holidays!</string>
    <string name="C6_site_PBaguette">https://www.facebook.com/PBPaloAlto</string>
    <string name="C6_location_PBaguette">37.4471832, -122.2308279</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 7 -->
    <string name="C7_name_BlueGarden">Blue Garden Cafe</string>
    <string name="C7_address_BlueGarden">75 Arbor Rd, Ste V, Menlo Park, CA 94025–5367</string>
    <string name="C7_desc_BlueGarden">JW Catering is a premiere catering company proudly serving the
        bay area for over 10 years. We are honored to be the food provider for the Blue Garden Cafe.</string>
    <string name="C7_site_BlueGarden">http://www.bluegardencafe.com/</string>
    <string name="C7_location_BlueGarden">37.4414235, -122.2491083</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 8 -->
    <string name="C8_name_BlueBottle">Blue Bottle Coffee</string>
    <string name="C8_address_BlueBottle">456 University Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94301–1812</string>
    <string name="C8_desc_BlueBottle">We work directly with farmers around the world to source the
        most delicious and sustainable coffees we can find. Then, we roast them to our exacting
        flavor standards, and serve them to you at peak deliciousness, hopefully alongside a good
        conversation and some friendly advice. We think it\'s a privilege to deliver the coffees we
        love, by farmers we admire, into your hands or onto your doorstep. Our people are the kindest,
        most hard working and talented in the business. We\'re an impossibly eclectic group of coffee
        experts, artists, writers, sensory scientists, bakers, designers, and all-around dreamers.</string>
    <string name="C8_site_BlueBottle">https://bluebottlecoffee.com/</string>
    <string name="C8_location_BlueBottle">37.4475588, -122.1617385</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 9 -->
    <string name="C9_name_Tootsies">Tootsies</string>
    <string name="C9_address_Tootsies">700 Welch Rd, Suite #150, Palo Alto, CA 94304–1502</string>
    <string name="C9_desc_Tootsies">Tootsie\'s is a hidden gem full of delicious eats and treats.
        Just outside the Stanford Mall you will find this charming rustic brick building with indoor
        and outdoor seating. We serve breakfast with a large variety of coffee options, brunch, and lunch.</string>
    <string name="C9_site_Tootsies">https://www.facebook.com/TootsiesBarn/</string>
    <string name="C9_location_Tootsies">37.4375753, -122.2430491</string>

    <!-- Coffee Shop No. 10 -->
    <string name="C10_name_Joanies">Joanie\'s Cafe</string>
    <string name="C10_address_Joanies">405 S California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94306-1832</string>
    <string name="C10_desc_Joanies">A classic American grill with a warm and inviting neighborhood
        feel. The relaxed setting offers casual, yet sophisticated, dining with a menu that
        highlights regional and seasonal ingredients. An extensive wine-by-the-glass and craft brew
        selection is also featured.Open for breakfast, lunch, dinner and late night snacks.</string>
    <string name="C10_site_Joanies">http://joaniescafepaloalto.com/</string>
    <string name="C10_location_Joanies">37.4263997, -122.1467714</string>

</resources>
